Stretch your hand!
Your blessing is as close as your mouth.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
It is the only part of your body where nobody teaches you the direction when you are eating.
It goes straight to your mouth, even in the dark.
If you are carrying food, you take it straight to your mouth.
Your blessing is as close as your mouth.
Tell your neighbour, "My blessing is as close as my mouth".
I can't hear you.
My blessing is as close as my mouth.
Don't let self-pity hold you back.
You are at the point of breakthrough right now.
I am telling you God's opinion.
You are at the point of breakthrough.
Yes. This is your breakthrough.
Are you ready?
Yes!
Right now, we will first of all rebuke whatever medium in your body that evil spirits are using to operate.
People sometimes would say, "I am hearing a voice".
Some would say, "My eye is shaking".
Some would say, "Something is talking in my stomach".
Some would say, "My leg is too heavy".
Any part of your system that evil spirits are using to operate,
be it your head, eye, ear, throat, tongue, hand,
begin to rebuke that spirit, in Jesus' name!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Open your lips and command out all spirits of sorcery, witchcraft and divination.
Command them out right now!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
All spirits of witchcraft, sorcery, and divination, in the name of Jesus, command them out!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
People would say, "I am addicted to talking too much, sleeping too much, eating too much".
You are addicted to smoking, drinking, fleshly desires.
All spirits of addiction in your life - open your lips and begin to rebuke them right now!
Rebuke it!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Whatever bad habit you are addicted to - all spirits of addiction, immorality -
open your lips and begin to rebuke that spirit of immorality, spirit of addiction, in the name of Jesus.
Open your lips and rebuke them!
Vomitting Poisonous Substances
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Wave your hand!
Begin to cancel every negative spirit standing against you.
Every spirit standing against you, cancel it!
Hallelujah!
Cancel the spirit.
Remember those countries that are trouble spots.
Pray for peace in troubled nations, in Jesus' name.
Pray for troubled nations.
Pray for God's intervention.
Remember your nation once again and wave your flag.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Pray for your nation and God's intervention.
Viewers all over the world, receive your portion.
Be delivered!
Be healed!
Whatever sickness, whatever name they call it -
never a sickness Jesus cannot heal, never a burden Jesus cannot bear,
never a disease Jesus cannot cure.
Be delivered in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Touch Your Screen By Faith, in Jesus' Name
Are you on the sickbed?
Dry bones rise again.
All spirits operating in your system, be delivered, in the name of Jesus!
Be cast out in the name of Jesus!
All spirits operating in your system, ears, throat, tongue, health,
be delivered in the name of Jesus!
Be cast out in the name of Jesus!
Come out!
In the name of Jesus.
Viewers all over the world, cover yourself with the blood of Jesus.
Let there be light in your soul.
Let there be light in your system.
Let there be light in your spirit.
Let there be light in your flesh.
Let there be light in your blood.
Let there be light in your fluids.
Let there be light in your bones.
Let there be light in your muscles.
Let there be light in your womb.
Let there be light.
In the name of Jesus Christ!
It is well.
In the name of Jesus Christ.
Right now begin to commit your business, career.
Good morning, my career. It is a new dawn.
My future, good morning. It is a new dawn.
My destiny, good morning. It is a new dawn.
It is a new dawn. Good morning!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Touch Your Screen By Faith, in Jesus' Name
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies, deliverances,
sermons and testimonies from The SCOAN.
Emmanuel TV - Changing lives, Changing nations, and Changing the world.
CR Robert Begier 15/04/2019